

# **SUMMARY**

A skilled full-stack web developer who is very passionate about computer science. Having a great experience in web development, he is stubborn to always excel at what he does and to stand out from the crowd.

Very dedicated, persistant, hard working and extremelely curious, he looks forward to always learn new things through new opportunities and to make the most out of them.

#### **SKILLS**

- IDE & Platforms:
  Visual Studio Code and Postman
- Programming languages:
  JavaScript and TypeScript
- Frameworks/ Libraries:
  ReactJS, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Three.js and Express.js
- Databases:
  Firebase, Oracle and MongoDB
- Other web related skills/technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, JWT, Next-Auth.js, PassportJS, Stripe

#### **OTHER SKILLS**

- Project management
- Time management
- Problem solving
- Scrum

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Arabic.
- French.
- English.

# **OUSSAMA DHRAIEF**

Full-Stack Web Developer

# **EDUCATION**

Higher Institute of Applied Science and Technology of Sousse.

Bachelor's degree of Computer Science (2019 - 2022).

#### **PROJECTS**

#### E-commerce website.

Developing and maintaining an E-commerce website using:

- Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Back-End: JavaScript, Firebase Realtime Database and Firebase Authentification.

Portfolio website.

Developing and maintaining a portfolio website using:

- Front-End: Next.js (ReactJS), Tailwind CSS, JavaScript and CSS3.
- Back-End: Next.js, Node.js and MongoDB.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **End of studies internship**

• QUICK Medical Services (Feb. 2022 - May 2022)

Developing and maintaining a website for selling medical and surgical instruments online:

 Next.js, ReactJS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Node.js and MongoDB, Next-Auth.js, EmailJS.

#### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

Dentrain UAE (July 2022 - August 2022)

Developing and maintaining a website for selling medical scrubs:

 ReactJS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, EmailJS, Node.js, MongoDB, Express.js, PassportJS, Stripe.

#### CONTACT

Website: www.oussama-dhraief.me Github: /oussamadhraief

E-mail: oussema.dhraief@gmail.com LinkedIn: /oussama-dhraief/

Phone number: +216 95 236 383